Mechanics Educational Society of America, Rome City Central (Rome, N.Y.) Records 5679
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mechanics Educational Society of America, Rome City Central (Rome, N.Y.) Records
1939-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mechanics Educational Society of America
5679
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Contracts, correspondence and records from the Mechanics Educational Society of America, Rome City Central (Rome, N.Y.)
3338512
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 18, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence 5238: Willard Eugene Hotchkiss Arbitration Awards and Papers 5619: ACWA Records 5679: Mechanics Educational Society of America, Rome City Central (Rome, N.Y.) Records 5809 mf: Adolph Germer Papers on Microfilm 6030: Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6035: Constitution Collection 6043 MB: Union Memorabilia Collection 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13)
Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Rome -- Local unions; Mechanics Educational Society of America. Rome City Central (Rome, N.Y.)
3338512
- AF of L. Brown, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AF of L, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Merger (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Copper and Brass Council (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Copper and Brass. UAW, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- DeBella, James, 1939-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6-11)
- Interstate. Reiss, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Interstate. Reiss. Notices to all local presidents, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Interstate. Reiss. W.L.B. Cases. Miscellaneous, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Interstate. Reiss. Handbills, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Interstate. Reiss., 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Interstate. Reiss. Area News, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- I.A.M. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Kozma, James, 1939-1959 (Box 1, Folder 19-23)
- Local 2. compliance, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Local 2. correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25-27)
- Local 2. contracts, 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 28-30)
- Local 2. contracts, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 2. Notices and Bulletins, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
- Local 6. contracts, 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Local 6. correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
- Local 10. compliance, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
- Local 10. contracts, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
- Local 10. correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
- Local 10. Jenny Industries, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Local 10. Jenny Industries. contracts, 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Local 10. Joseph Perfetti Benevolent, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Local 10. Notices and Financial reports, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
- Local 10. Pension contracts, 1953-1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Local 10. Pension Plan, 1951-1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Local 10. Plant guard unit, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Local 10a. Ft. Stanwix Mfg. Co. correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Local 10a. Ft. Stanwix Mfg. Co. contracts, 1955-1958 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local 13. correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Local 14. compliance, 1952-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4-7)
- Local 14. contracts, 1950-1968 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
- Local 14. contract negotiations, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Local 14. correspondence, 1950-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12-17)
- Local 14. Grievance Nos. 89-105 (Box 3, Folder 18-33)
- Local 14. N. Arnold Tolles. Arbitration, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Local 14. Vacation Pay. Arbitration, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Local 14. Young Case, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Local 15. American Brass, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Local 16. Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Local 17. Basis for NLRB Protest. Perth Amboy, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Local 17. Contracts, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
- Local 17. Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
- Local 17. Election, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Local 17. Election, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
- Local 17. Handbills, 1951-1955 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
- Local 17. Office, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Local 17. Savoia, Mike, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Local 17. Steelworkers, 1952-1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Local 21, 1945-1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Local 23, 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Local 24. Board Cases (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Local 24. Correspondence & Misc., 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Local 25. Watertown (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Local 25. Watertown. Contracts (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Local 29. American Emblem. Correspondence, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 7-9)
- Local 29. Contracts, 1942-1949 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Trusts (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Unemployment Insurance Forms (Box 5, Folder 12)